Service : VSS is currently Stopped, should be Running
Setting VSS to Running
Action failed Service VSS is still Stopped, should be Running
Service : XblGameSave is currently Running, should be Stopped
Setting XblGameSave to Stopped
Action was succesful Service XblGameSave is now Stopped
Service : XblAuthManager is currently Running, should be Stopped
Setting XblAuthManager to Stopped
Action was succesful Service XblAuthManager is now Stopped
